<spaceship>
    <room>
        <name>bridge</name>
        <description>You are on the bridge of the Vostok-32. Cracked monitors litter the floor. Broken cables fall loosely from the ceiling, their ends sparking with ungrounded electrical currents. The emergency LEDs give the room a faint, pulsing red glow...aside from the monitor displaying the bright blip of an unknown lifeform.</description>
        <items>key helmet</items>
        <west>gym</west>
        <south>kitchen</south>
        <east>server</east>
        <north>game</north>
        <usable>none</usable>
        <challenge>none</challenge>
    </room>
    <room>
        <name>game</name>
        <description>This is where all the fun in space happens. You get to match colors!</description>
        <items>cube</items>
        <west>none</west>
        <south>bridge</south>
        <east>none</east>
        <north>none</north>
        <usable>none</usable>
        <challenge>match</challenge>
    </room>
    <room>
        <name>gym</name>
        <description>You are in the ship's small gym. Most of the equipment remains securely fastened despite the destruction throughout the Vostok. A large poster hanging over the rack of dumbbells draws your eye to it: an image of Sputnik-1, the first artificial Earth satellite and a point of great pride for all of Russia.</description>
        <items>tools</items>
        <east>bridge</east>
        <west>none</west>
        <south>none</south>
        <north>none</north>
        <usable>none</usable>
        <challenge>alien</challenge>
    </room>
    <room>
        <name>kitchen</name>
        <description>You are in the mess hall. It is an absolute disaster: bent metal and broken ceramics cover the dura-steel floors. Strangely, a plate of cooked broccoli seems to have survived the wreckage and sits unassumingly on the only upright table in the room.</description>
        <items>broccoli</items>
        <north>bridge</north>
        <south>none</south>
        <east>none</east>
        <west>none</west>
        <usable>none</usable>
        <challenge>none</challenge>
    </room>
    <room>
        <name>server</name>
        <description>You are in the ships Onboard DataCenter(ODC). Emergency lights blink red and yellow on every access port. A lone screen flashes a command line interface with a small green underscore, ready for user input.</description>
        <items>keyboard</items>
        <north>none</north>
        <south>none</south>
        <east>none</east>
        <west>bridge</west>
        <usable>key</usable>
        <challenge>hacking</challenge>
    </room>
</spaceship>